briggsandstratton.com 2016-04-07

# Website Privacy Policy | Briggs & Stratton

Last Updated 12/11/2015

**PRIVACY POLICY  
**We take your privacy seriously, and we want you to know how we collect, use, share and protect your personal information.

**This Privacy Policy tells you:**

  * What information we collect
  * How we use that information
  * How we may share that information
  * How we protect your information
  * Your choices regarding your personal information

This Policy applies only to personal information that we collect on the website briggsandstratton.com (the “Site”). This Policy does not apply to other brands or sites owned by Briggs & Stratton Corporation or its subsidiaries or affiliates, such as Snapper (snapper.com), Simplicity (simplicitymfg.com, or Murray (murray.com), among others, each of which has its own privacy policy. 

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**Information You Give Us**   
We collect information that you enter on our Site. For example, we collect information from you when you place an order, create an account, e-mail us with a question, create a Wish List, write a review, or use any of our services.

The information we collect from you may include :

  * Your name
  * Your mailing address
  * Your e-mail address
  * Your phone number
  * Your credit card number and other payment information
  * Demographic and lifestyle information, such as age, personal interests and product preferences

**Information From Other Sources**   
We may receive information about you from third parties who help us update, expand and analyze our records, and improve our website experience. We do not use this information to identify you individually, but it does reflect some of your activities on the Internet, such as the web sites you visited immediately before visiting the Site or links available at other websites which directed you to the Site.

**Briggs & Stratton SMS Alerts**  
If you have opted-in to receive Briggs & Stratton SMS alerts, you can discontinue receiving SMS messages by texting **STOP** to 64586. For additional help, text **HELP** to 64586 or call us at 1-800-444-7774.  
**Msg &Data Rates May Apply.**

**Do We Use Cookies?  
**Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits to our Site and compile aggregate data about Site traffic and Site interactions so that we can offer better Site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our Site visitors. These service providers are permitted to use the information collected on our behalf only to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies by adjusting your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.

We do not allow third parties to collect individually identifiable information about you or your online activities at this site or across different sites over time by using cookies or by any other means. 

**Your 'Do Not Track' Browser Setting  
** We support the Do Not Track (DNT) browser setting. DNT is a preference you can set in your browser's settings to let the websites you visit know that you do not want the sites collecting your personally identifiable information. We will not collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services regardless of whether you choose the DNT browser preference.

**Log Files  
**The Site uses Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information. An Internet Service Provider ("ISP") typically assigns a random dynamic IP address at the time of your dial-up. For local area network ("LAN"), DSL, or cable modem users, a static IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. We may record the IP addresses of visitors to the Site. While an IP address may reveal your ISP or geographic area, we cannot determine your identity solely based upon your IP address. Other web sites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those web sites and their pages, but these IP addresses are never associated with specific Internet users.

**Public Forums**   
Our Site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. In addition, your participation in any blog or community form through the Site is subject to the Terms of Use.

**HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
**We use the information we collect to serve our customers and improve their experience at the Site. Some examples include:

  * Fulfilling orders and requests for products, services or information
  * Tracking and confirming online orders
  * Improving customer service
  * Marketing and advertising products and services
  * Conducting research and analysis
  * Establishing and managing your accounts with us
  * Communicating about special events, sweepstakes, promotions and surveys
  * Identifying you on our Site and tailoring messages and offers to you based on your interactions with us online
  * Facilitating interactions with Briggs & Stratton and others, such as enabling you to email a link to a friend or post a link on Facebook
  * Continuously evaluating and improving our online user experience

**Surveys & Contests**   
From time-to-time our Site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary, and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as zip code or age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use of, and your satisfaction with, this Site.

**Supplementation of Information**   
In order for this Site to enhance its ability to tailor the Site to an individual's preference, we may combine information about the purchasing habits of users with similar information from our merchant partners to create a personalized user profile. When a user makes a purchase from our merchant partners, the companies collect and share that purchase information with us so we can tailor the Site to our users' preferences.

**Data Retention**   
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**HOW WE SHARE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
**We do not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties. Briggs & Stratton Corporation, or its subsidiaries or affiliates, are the owners of related brands, including but not limited to, Snapper, Simplicity, Brute, Murray, and Victa. As such, if you provide information on any of the websites owned or operated by Briggs & Stratton Corporation, or its subsidiaries or affiliates, this information may be combined or shared among other current or future Briggs & Stratton Corporation entities, including subsidiaries and affiliates.

We also will share your information with third-party service providers under contract with Briggs & Stratton Corporation, or its subsidiaries or affiliates, to help us provide services to you. Such third-party service providers include, for example, credit card payment processors, e-mail marketers, website analytics providers, and chat communications providers. We also will share your information with third parties who sell products or services that we believe might be of interest to you, such as independent dealers who sell our products and services and merchant partners who provide related products and services, such as gardening equipment or supplies. 

Sometimes we may be required to share personal information in response to a court order, subpoena, civil discovery request, other legal process, or as otherwise required by law. We may disclose account and other personal information when we believe disclosure is necessary to comply with the law or protect the rights, property, or safety of Briggs and Stratton Corporation, its subsidiaries or affiliates, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We may disclose your personal information to prospective purchasers of any interest in Briggs & Stratton Corporation, its subsidiaries or affiliates, or their assets.

**Third party links**   
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our Site. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Site and welcome any feedback about these other sites.

**CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE/YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS  
**California residents who use this Site may request that we provide certain information regarding our disclosure of the user’s personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. You can make such a request by e-mail or by mail to: 

Briggs & Stratton Corporate Headquarters   
P.O. Box 702  
Milwaukee, WI, 53201

**CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE  
**We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our Site, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. If you are under the age of 13, you are not authorized to use this Site.

**HOW WE PROTECT THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
**We work to protect the security of your personal information. During transmission of personal information between you and our Site, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software to encrypt information you input. During the order process, we reveal only the last four digits of your credit card number when confirming an order. The entire credit card number is, of course, submitted to the appropriate credit card company during order processing, but we do not store your credit card information on our servers.

All of our users' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. All employees with access to personal information are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. After a new policy is added, these employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to enhance protection for our customers' information. Finally, the servers that we use to store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure, restricted access area.

**YOUR CHOICES REGARDING THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
**You may choose to:

  * Stop receiving marketing or promotional e-mails by clicking the unsubscribe link in the e-mail
  * Update and correct your personal information by logging into your profile via My Account and going to the 'My Profile' page

**HAVE QUESTIONS  
**If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, we'll do our best to answer them. Here's how to contact us:

**Phone:**   
1-800-444-7774

**Online:  
** <http://www.briggsandstratton.com/us/en/support/ask-briggs>

**Mailing Address:**   
Briggs & Stratton Corporate Headquarters   
P.O. Box 702  
Milwaukee, WI, 53201

**PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES  
**If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page and update the Privacy Policy modification date above. If we materially change this Privacy Policy in a way that affects how we use or disclose your personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting a notice of such changes before making them and by stating the effective date of the changes.

Firmwide:125156402.1 052740.1000
